const quizArr = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the Arabic name for Prophet Ibrahim?",
    options: {
      A: "Musa",
      B: "Isa",
      C: "Ibrahim",
      D: "Nuh",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which city is associated with Prophet Ibrahim's early life?",
    options: {
      A: "Mecca",
      B: "Medina",
      C: "Ur",
      D: "Jerusalem",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What was the main message of Prophet Ibrahim?",
    options: {
      A: "Worship of many gods",
      B: "Monotheism (belief in one God)",
      C: "Wealth and prosperity",
      D: "Revenge against enemies",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Who was Prophet Ibrahim's first son?",
    options: {
      A: "Ismail (Ishmael)",
      B: "Ishaq (Isaac)",
      C: "Yusuf (Joseph)",
      D: "Yaqub (Jacob)",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What test did Allah give to Prophet Ibrahim regarding his son Ismail?",
    options: {
      A: "To build a Kaaba",
      B: "To sacrifice him",
      C: "To travel to Egypt",
      D: "To fast for a month",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What did Allah provide to Prophet Ibrahim as a substitute for Ismail during the sacrifice?",
    options: {
      A: "A lamb",
      B: "A goat",
      C: "A cow",
      D: "A bird",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which significant structure did Prophet Ibrahim and his son Ismail build?",
    options: {
      A: "The Temple of Solomon",
      B: "The Kaaba",
      C: "The Al-Aqsa Mosque",
      D: "The Great Pyramid",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the name of the festival that commemorates the willingness of Prophet Ibrahim to sacrifice his son?",
    options: {
      A: "Eid al-Fitr",
      B: "Eid al-Adha",
      C: "Mawlid",
      D: "Ashura",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which king opposed Prophet Ibrahim and his message of monotheism?",
    options: {
      A: "Pharaoh",
      B: "Nimrod",
      C: "Nebuchadnezzar",
      D: "Herod",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the significance of Prophet Ibrahim in Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "He is considered the father of the prophets.",
      B: "He is the last prophet.",
      C: "He is the first Muslim.",
      D: "He is the founder of Judaism.",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
];

